RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
- Series 16. Secretary, 1980-1998; 31 cubic feet
  - Anthony V. Milano, 1980-1990
    - Subject Files
      - 1987 OPM Office of the Secretary and Budget Division; Agency Audit Reports; Departments of Administrative Services, Aging, Agriculture, Children & Youth Services (DCYS), Consumer Protection, Correction, and Economic Development. (Box 15)
      - 1987 OPM Business Office, Comprehensive Planning, Justice Planning, Intergovernmental Relations, Energy, Management & Evaluation; Standard & Poor's; Departments of Education, Environmental Protection, Health Services, Higher Education, Housing, Income Maintenance, Mental Retardation, Public Safety, Revenue Services, and Transportation. (Box 16)
      - 1987 Attorney General, Comptroller, CT Housing Finance Authority (CHFA), Council of State Governments, Governor's Office, Management Advisory Council (MAC), and Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 17)
      - 1987 National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO), Publications, Secretary of the State, Transportation Accountability Board (TAB), and the Treasurer's Office. (Box 18)
      - 1988 & 1989 OPM Office of the Secretary, Anthony V. Milano (AVM), Gordon J. Frassinelli (GJF), Budget & Financial Management, Business Office, Census Conference, and Comprehensive Planning. (Box 19)
      - 1988 & 1989 OPM Comprehensive Planning Continued, Energy, and Intergovernmental Relations; Departments of Aging, Banking, Children & Youth Services (DCYS), Consumer Protection, Correction, Economic Development, Education, Environmental Protection, Health Services, Higher Education, Housing, Human Resources, Income Maintenance, Insurance, Labor Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Motor Vehicle, Public Safety, Public Works, Revenue Services, Transportation, and Veterans Home & Hospital. (Box 20)
      - 1989 & 1989 Attorney General, Bridgeport Financial Review Board, Comptroller, CT Housing Finance Authority (CHFA: 12/88, 4/;89, & 10/89). Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO) (Box 21)
      - 1988 & 1989 Secretary of the State, Council of State Governments, Treasurer, Governor's Task Force on Drug Trafficking, Drugs Don't Work, CT Housing Finance Authority Report, and Budget Auditors Report. (Box 22)
      - 1988 & 1989 Budget Auditors Reports Continued, Various Reports, and Shearson Lehman Brothers. (Box 23)
      - 1986 Office of Policy & Management, and Budget & Financial Management (Box 24)
      - January through May 1990 general monthly correspondence. (Box 25)
      - June 1990 general monthly correspondence. (Box 26)
      - July and August 1990 general monthly correspondence. (Box 27)
  - William Cibes, Reginald Jones, Michael Koslowski, Lori Aronson (Deputy), Donald Downs (Deputy), 1991-1998; 2003-009
    - Ongoing Policy Issue Files (Box 1-4)
      Unarranged.
- Series 17. Governor's Council on Voluntary Action, 1979-1991; 1992-035; 11 cubic feet
  - Administrative Files and Annual Conference Materials, 1979-1991
    - Annual Conference Files, 1991 (Box 1-2)
    - Annual Conference Files and Tapes, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Annual Conference Files, 1989 (Box 4)
    - State Agencies with Volunteer Programs, 1981-1990 (Box 5)
    - Annual Conference Files, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Annual Conference Files, 1979-1987 (Box 7)
    - Assorted Council Files Records, 1979-1991 (Box 8)
      - Informational, Educational Presentation about Volunteerism in America, 1 videocassette (Box 8)
      - Volunteerism & The Corporate Sector in America, 1 videocassette (Box 8)
      - Newsletter, 5 computer disks (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Volunteer News, 1979-1990 (Box 8)
      - VOLNET from The National Volunteer Center, Virginia, 1988 (Box 8)
      - VOLNET from The National Volunteer Center, Virginia, 1989 (Box 8)
      - VOLNET from The National Volunteer Center, Virginia, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
      - Governor's Council Board Minutes of the Meetings, 1981-1979 (Box 8)
      - Governor's Council Board Minutes of the Meetings, 1985-1982 (Box 8)
      - Governor's Council Board Minutes of the Meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 8)
      - Governor's Council Board Minutes of the Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
      - Past Conference Brochures, 1983-1991 (Box 8)
      - Courtney W. Gardner - Correspondence (Box 8)
      - 1991 Governor's Laurel Awards - forms, pictures (Box 8)
      - Photographs and Press Clippings (Box 8)
      - Materials for Awards Presentation at Governor's Office, 1985 April 24 (Box 8)
      - Governor Ella T. Grasso (Box 8)
    - Laurel Award Nominees, 1988-1991 (Box 9)
      - Pfizer, Inc., Groton (Box 9)
      - Phoenix Mutual Insurance Company, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, East Hartford (Box 9)
      - Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 9)
      - The Stanley Works, New Britain (Box 9)
      - Union Carbide Corporation, Danbury (Box 9)
      - Waring Products Division, New Hartford (Box 9)
      - Newman's Own, Inc., Westport (Box 9)
      - Olin Corporation, Stamford (Box 9)
      - People's Bank of Bridgeport (Box 9)
      - Pepperidge Farm, Inc., Norwalk (Box 9)
      - J. C. Company, Manchester (Box 9)
      - McDonald's Owner Association, Wallingford (Box 9)
      - Merchants Bank & Trust Company, Norwalk (Box 9)
      - Middlesex Mutual Assurance Company (Box 9)
      - Mintz & Hoke Advertising, Avon (Box 9)
      - B. Perkins & Company, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Champion International, Stamford (Box 9)
      - Chase Broadcasting, Stamford (Box 9)
      - Cigna Insurance Company, Bloomfield (Box 9)
      - Connecticut Bank & Trust Company, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Connecticut Minority Business Development Center (Box 9)
      - Connecticut Mutual Insurance Company (Box 9)
      - Ensign-Bickford Industries, Simsbury (Box 9)
      - Fairfield County Typographers, Westport (Box 9)
      - Fleet Bank, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Gateway Bank, South Norwalk (Box 9)
      - The Hartford Whalers, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Loctite Corporation, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Aetna Life & Casualty Insurance, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Aetna Taking Part, 1988 (Box 9)
      - The Hartford Courant (Box 9)
      - The Hartford Insurance Group (Box 9)
      - The Hartford House (Box 9)
      - Northeast Utilities, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Society for Savings Bank, Hartford (Box 9)
      - United Technologies Corporation, Hartford (Box 9)
      - Travelers Insurance Company, Hartford (Box 9)
      - United Illuminating, New Haven (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Director's Files, 1986-1990 (Box 10-11)
- Series 18. Department of Planning and Energy Policy, 1977; 1999-036; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Report
    - Energy Conservation Plan, 1977
- Series 19. Office of Labor Relations, 1994-1995; 1999-076
  Stored in a shared box.
  - Arbitration Awards, 1994-1995; 3 folders
- Series 20. Specialized State-Operated Services Committee of the Juvenile Justice Reorganization Plan, 1994-1995; 2001-070; 0.50 cubic feet
  - Records
    - Community Based Programs, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Facilities, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Files, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Mental Health, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Substance Abuse, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Senator Thomas Upson Files, 1995; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Background Information, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Background Information, 1995; 2 folders (Box 1)
- Series 21. Blue Ribbon Commission on Housing, 1987-1988; 2001-074; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Joan Maloney Files, 1987 October-1988
    - Membership (Box 1)
    - Agendas/Minutes (Box 1)
    - Low-Income Subcommittee (Box 1)
    - Moderate-Income Subcommittee (Box 1)
- Series 22. Connecticut Census Data Center, 1985; 1988; 3 cubic feet
  - Social Indicators for Planning and Evaluation, 1985; 2004-029; 2 cubic feet
    - State of Connecticut (Box 1)
    - Technical Report, Original (Box 1)
    - ERRATA (Box 1)
    - Order Form (Box 1)
    - Fairfield County (Box 1)
    - Hartford County (Box 1)
    - Litchfield County (Box 1)
    - Middlesex County (Box 1)
    - New London County (Box 1)
    - New Haven County (Box 1)
    - Tolland County (Box 1)
    - Windham County (Box 1)
    - Bridgeport SMSA (Box 1)
    - Bristol SMSA (Box 1)
    - Danbury SMSA (Box 1)
    - Hartford SMSA (Box 1)
    - Meriden SMSA (Box 1)
    - New Britain SMSA (Box 1)
    - New Haven - West Haven SMSA (Box 1)
    - Norwalk SMSA (Box 1)
    - Stamford SMSA (Box 1)
    - Waterbury SMSA (Box 1)
    - SDA-1 Bridgeport - Ansonia (Box 1)
    - SDA-2 Bristol - New Britain (Box 1)
    - SDA-3 Danbury - Torrington (Box 1)
    - SDA-4 Danielson - Windham Consortium (Box 1)
    - SDA-5 Hartford Consortium (Box 1)
    - SDA-6 Meriden - Middletown (Box 1)
    - SDA-7 New Haven Consortium (Box 1)
    - SDA-8 New London - Norwich (Box 1)
    - Ansonia (Box 1)
    - Avon (Box 1)
    - Berlin (Box 1)
    - Bethel (Box 1)
    - Bloomfield (Box 1)
    - Bridgeport (Box 1)
    - Bristol (Box 1)
    - Brookfield (Box 1)
    - Cheshire (Box 1)
    - Clinton (Box 1)
    - Cromwell (Box 1)
    - Danbury (Box 1)
    - Darien (Box 1)
    - Derby (Box 1)
    - East Hartford (Box 1)
    - East Haven (Box 1)
    - East Lyme (Box 1)
    - Enfield (Box 1)
    - Fairfield (Box 1)
    - Farmington (Box 1)
    - Glastonbury (Box 1)
    - Greenwich (Box 1)
    - Groton (Box 1)
    - Guilford (Box 1)
    - Hamden (Box 1)
    - Hartford (Box 1)
    - Killingly (Box 1)
    - Ledyard (Box 1)
    - Madison (Box 1)
    - Manchester (Box 1)
    - Mansfield (Box 1)
    - Meriden (Box 1)
    - Middletown (Box 1)
    - Milford (Box 1)
    - Monroe (Box 1)
    - Montville (Box 1)
    - Naugatuck (Box 1)
    - New Britain (Box 1)
    - New Canaan (Box 2)
    - New Fairfield (Box 2)
    - New Haven (Box 2)
    - Newington (Box 2)
    - New London (Box 2)
    - New Milford (Box 2)
    - Newtown (Box 2)
    - North Branford (Box 2)
    - North Haven (Box 2)
    - Norwalk (Box 2)
    - Norwich (Box 2)
    - Orange (Box 2)
    - Plainfield (Box 2)
    - Plainville (Box 2)
    - Plymouth (Box 2)
    - Ridgefield (Box 2)
    - Rocky Hill (Box 2)
    - Seymour (Box 2)
    - Shelton (Box 2)
    - Simsbury (Box 2)
    - Southbury (Box 2)
    - Southington (Box 2)
    - South Windsor (Box 2)
    - Stamford (Box 2)
    - Stonington (Box 2)
    - Stratford (Box 2)
    - Torrington (Box 2)
    - Trumbull (Box 2)
    - Vernon (Box 2)
    - Wallingford (Box 2)
    - Waterbury (Box 2)
    - Waterford (Box 2)
    - Watertown (Box 2)
    - West Hartford (Box 2)
    - West Haven (Box 2)
    - Westport (Box 2)
    - Westport (Box 2)
    - Wethersfield (Box 2)
    - Wilton (Box 2)
    - Winchester (Box 2)
    - Windham (Box 2)
    - Windsor (Box 2)
    - Windsor Locks (Box 2)
    - Wolcott (Box 2)
    - Labor Area Market Reports (LMA's) (Box 2)
    - 1984 Estimates of Social Indicators (Box 2)
  - Job Training Partnership Act Eligibility Report, 1988; 2004-030; 1 cubic foot
    - Job Training Partnership Act (Box 1)
    - State Congregate Housing Program (Box 1)
    - Private Industry Council / Job Training Act (Box 1)
    - JTPA - State Summary Intro & Glossary (Box 1)
      - JTPAA Report Problems (Box 1)
      - JTPAA Glossary (Box 1)
      - JTPAA Introduction (Box 1)
    - JTPAA Service Delivery Areas (Box 1)
      - SDA-1 Bridgeport, Norwalk, Stamford, Valley SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-2 New Britain, Bristol SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-3 Danbury, Torrington SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-4 Northeast Area SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-5 Hartford Area SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-6 Middlesex Area SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-7 New Haven Area SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-8 Southeast Area SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - SDA-9 Waterbury Area SDA, 1988 February (Box 1)
    - JTPAA Microdata Regions (Box 1)
      - 001 Stamford town, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 002 Darien area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 003 Westport area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 004 Bridgeport town, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 005 Fairfield area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 006 Stratford, Shelton, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 007 New Haven town, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 008 West Haven area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 009 Meriden area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 010 Madison area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 011 Middlesex area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 012 New London area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 013 New London area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 014 Windham/Tolland County area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 015 Hartford town, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 016 West Hartford area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 017 Farmington area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 018 East Hartford area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 019 Glastonbury area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 020 New Britain area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 021 Southington area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 022 Waterbury town, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 023 Cheshire area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 024 Danbury area, 1988 February (Box 1)
      - 025 Litchfield County Remainder, 1988 February (Box 1)
- Series 23. Energy Advisory Board, 1974-2003; 2006-003; 2 cubic feet
  - Minutes
    - 1974-1988 (Box 1)
    - 1991-2003 (Box 2)
- Series 24. Office of Family Support, 2001-2004
  Inventory of Office of Family Support Records